{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":0,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:02 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:02 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:03 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:03 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:03 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:03 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:03 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:05 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:06 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:07 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:09 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:10 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:10 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:10 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:12 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:13 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:13 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:15 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:16 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:17 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:17 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926080233,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926090353},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-10122],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:18 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926090401,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926098844},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-8445],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926089680,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926099252},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-9573],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:19 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926090070,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926101789},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-11720],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926093444,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926100279},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-6846],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:20 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:24 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:25 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:25 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:25 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:26 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:26 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:26 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:27 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:28 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:28 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:29 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:30 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926101289,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926111004},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-9721],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926105199,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926114734},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-9538],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926098777,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926112059},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-13285],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926089536,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926111743},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-22209],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926105215,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926114066},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-8853],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926105926,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926114869},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-8949],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926098829,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926116140},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-17316],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926100174,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926115351},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-15180],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926100778,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926116386},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-15609],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926109008,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926117175},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-8171],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926096119,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926117754},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-21635],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:37 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926098079,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926118955},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-20877],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926101259,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926119290},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-27605],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926110899,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926119931},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-9038],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926102303,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926120045},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-24590],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926092357,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926113262},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-31027],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926114858,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926123853},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-8996],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926108064,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926122802},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-14739],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926109675,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926121179},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-11511],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926115667,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926123438},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-7777],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926107327,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926124282},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16959],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926114073,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926125335},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-24548],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926118604,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926133097},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-14497],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:44 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926173920,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926183929},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-10017],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926100854,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926125365},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-32956],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926108693,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926125542},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16852],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:45 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:46 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926115028,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926126747},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-11724],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926104482,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926127296},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-22817],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926103803,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926129685},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-37602],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:48 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:50 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:50 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:50 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926115164,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926131350},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16192],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:51 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926102257,"answerTime":1520926132260},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926109809,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926132910},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-30009],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-23104],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926113344,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926131531},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-18188],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926116763,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926137453},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-30229],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926114282,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926134399},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-20119],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926117376,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926134107},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16735],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926122059,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926134275},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-36807],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926106045,"answerTime":1520926136063},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-30024],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:55 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:56 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926113751,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926136584},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-45042],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926131352,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926136886},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-5534],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926113015,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926137628},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-34335],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926115271,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926130190},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-45946],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926125820,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926139337},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-13519],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520922521726,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922538638},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16914],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926116887,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926138650},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-30713],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926127659,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926138800},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-44097],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:28:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926185951,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926199409},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-23476],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926124816,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926141471},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-31395],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926134536,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926144844},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-10309],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926112468,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926140396},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-27938],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926138587,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926140450},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926212456,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926225239},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-46905],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-12785],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926127343,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926142418},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-39625],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926121943,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926142602},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-29698],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520922512764,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922542330},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-29568],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926126599,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926145008},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-18417],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926120964,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926144836},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-44750],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926125454,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926144066},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-26390],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926126289,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926145044},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-35714],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926116073,"answerTime":1520926146082},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-38867],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926128759,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926146375},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-29341],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926117363,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926146634},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-44451],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926118149,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926148029},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-47196],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:06 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926118394,"answerTime":1520926148394},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-45611],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926141868,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926148603},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-6740],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926121294,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926148546},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-54858],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926119182,"answerTime":1520926149184},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-38177],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926125856,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926151903},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-35044],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926119757,"answerTime":1520926149760},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-51640],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926142455,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926149289},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-53739],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926201421,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926208812},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-30867],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926126919,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926143540},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16624],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:10 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926135108,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926159412},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-38802],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926139680,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926150416},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-10737],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926138893,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926151200},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-17841],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520922540646,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922551912},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-28180],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926127550,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926152135},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-41438],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926135623,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926152548},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16928],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926136412,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926153138},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-36846],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926132206,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926146294},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:14 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:14 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-60034],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:14 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926123196,"answerTime":1520926153200},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-41533],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926146846,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926156106},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-54011],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926140659,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926156115},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-46170],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926143917,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926156448},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-12532],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926136131,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926155907},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-36515],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926143488,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926157133},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-45041],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:16 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926093315,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926116124},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:17 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:17 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-22810],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926133540,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926156427},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-41076],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926144437,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926159227},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-54417],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926148390,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926159026},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-39977],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926129303,"answerTime":1520926159304},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-52825],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926141340,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926160296},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-32475],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926134920,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926159586},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-47774],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926151297,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926158732},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-61174],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926146851,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926163871},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-27330],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926131686,"answerTime":1520926161690},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-67608],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926153698,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926164164},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-10469],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926147048,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926161303},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-49970],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926144609,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926161992},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-47081],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926133366,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926162713},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-45540],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926139471,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926166847},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:23 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:23 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-57606],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:23 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926150619,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926163532},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:23 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:23 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-19654],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:23 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926136284,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926163650},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-64175],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926146078,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926163688},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-44001],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926134269,"answerTime":1520926164270},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-60013],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:24 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926210824,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926224235},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-44279],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926165126,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926166295},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:26 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:26 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-1172],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:26 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:26 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926140807,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926167070},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-70360],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926139633,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926167276},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-61979],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926157875,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926175672},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-17799],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926160736,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926166870},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-67308],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926138089,"answerTime":1520926168105},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-60044],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926153206,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926167478},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-32113],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926150033,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926169843},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-67007],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926155055,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926169173},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-14124],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926154787,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926169365},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-14580],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926161427,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926177747},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-55124],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520922553916,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922569798},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-44062],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:29 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926147238,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926172221},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-24985],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926154557,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926171632},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-34003],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926152420,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926171054},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-29372],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926168873,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926171220},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926169283,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926172113},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-69655],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-64810],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926150375,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1520926172715},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-22343],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926155148,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926173240},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-54939],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926193213,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1520926213127},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-19915],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926154141,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926172689},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-59988],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926158463,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926173375},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-27445],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926142424,"answerTime":1520926172428},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-57954],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926227249,"answerTime":1520926257251},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-42806],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926148093,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926174154},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-64928],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926158431,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926171931},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-54576],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926166174,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926177684},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-21979],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926352058,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926372178},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-20124],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926165886,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926178251},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-39697],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520922544341,"answerTime":1520922574348},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-59580],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926164727,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926175413},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-56228],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926173226,"answer":{"choice":"Petra"},"answerTime":1520926174776},"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-71205],"sessionId":"1","userId":8,"instanceId":"bZp8wenNruKnFMnAB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926151193,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926176006},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-62991],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926153905,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926178677},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-59816],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926147022,"answerTime":1520926177024},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-48425],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926159736,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926176398},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-16665],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926148642,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926176618},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-72427],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:36 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926161036,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926178274},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-57215],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926163696,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926179503},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-83416],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926162196,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1520926179058},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-16866],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926151769,"answer":{"choice":"Iris"},"answerTime":1520926179585},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-79457],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926150404,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926179805},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-75012],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926156637,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1520926180448},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-23812],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520922378263,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922387185},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-8923],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926162308,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926181501},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-51668],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926150553,"answerTime":1520926180554},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-84862],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926165540,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926180921},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-35035],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926159150,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926182050},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-67942],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926161600,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926181729},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-67904],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926161330,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926182088},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-73583],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926145556,"answerTime":1520926175562},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-46631],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926171373,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926183635},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-26846],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926175387,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926184087},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-36145],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926158121,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926184245},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-72295],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926155249,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926182984},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-69269],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926169493,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926184398},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-47018],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:45 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926148298,"answerTime":1520926178302},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-90040],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520922571802,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520922586616},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-58878],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:46 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926179695,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926190572},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-32857],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926169076,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926187734},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-89019],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926180488,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926188097},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-7610],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926173639,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926188036},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-48400],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926158117,"answerTime":1520926188120},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-84021],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926157941,"answerTime":1520926187954},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-66542],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926165670,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926188573},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-87080],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926161237,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926189748},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-82929],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926174235,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926189923},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-40674],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926168306,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926189535},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-22401],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926118127,"answerTime":1520926148130},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-52813],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926163307,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926191088},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-77751],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926174119,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926191267},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-81959],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926165700,"answer":{"choice":"Kevin"},"answerTime":1520926191099},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-69401],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926175253,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926194209},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-73896],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926163996,"answerTime":1520926193997},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:54 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:54 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-77086],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926177677,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926203379},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-43501],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926168861,"answerTime":1520926198861},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-87611],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926171199,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926196491},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-39416],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926171847,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926197988},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-93149],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926166278,"answerTime":1520926196279},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-90016],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:56 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926179761,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926205309},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-80672],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926178010,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926197506},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-82489],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926226243,"answerTime":1520926256246},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-74299],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926186253,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926197899},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-83942],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926178410,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926197972},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-36230],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926174462,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926197146},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-80640],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926173062,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926197888},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-54199],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926185646,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926199068},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-40269],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926174601,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926199537},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-24940],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926174037,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926199643},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-25609],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926190099,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926200020},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-17532],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926182927,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926199535},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-51644],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:29:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926170128,"answerTime":1520926200137},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-90056],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926174729,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926200291},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-47906],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926188645,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926199410},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-10767],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926179040,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926201958},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-71344],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926177421,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926201457},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-80265],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926184073,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926202268},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-86137],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926192585,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926205301},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-45574],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926374191,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926400621},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-46556],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926180293,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926203647},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-80569],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520922389190,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922411144},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-30878],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926183504,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926205650},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-73814],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926180259,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926208425},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-67864],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926174699,"answerTime":1520926204701},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926215130,"answerTime":1520926245132},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-49919],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-89998],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926191937,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926205512},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-54249],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926176159,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926205840},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-94609],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926259288,"answerTime":1520926289290},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-72823],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926173948,"answerTime":1520926203949},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-84580],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926186092,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926206670},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-56723],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926191540,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926206747},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-37609],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520918990251,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520919003993},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-13743],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520922576364,"answerTime":1520922606364},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-89583],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926182452,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926207233},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-48593],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926180678,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926209591},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-88729],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:07 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:07 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926181590,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926208548},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-106415],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926178626,"answerTime":1520926208628},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-102430],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926181066,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926208669},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-44470],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926177569,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926202146},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-71209],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926181812,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926210139},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-103339],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926181517,"answerTime":1520926211529},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-113429],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926184094,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926210690},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-100180],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926183736,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926211749},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-95918],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926199990,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926212833},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-49074],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926200882,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926216515},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-103245],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926182562,"answerTime":1520926212562},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-114865],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926202628,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926214291},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-11667],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926184991,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926212093},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-96373],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926190041,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926215058},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-73418],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926202022,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926215697},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-31207],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926186401,"answerTime":1520926216416},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-77035],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926190137,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926217383},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-111268],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926201416,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926216270},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-25621],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926190587,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926217085},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-113579],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926180326,"answerTime":1520926210341},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-120058],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520922588622,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520922618416},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-88672],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926189739,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926218682},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-117963],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926201543,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926219077},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-42474],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926190278,"answerTime":1520926220279},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-30007],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926198287,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926218788},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-110517],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926189990,"answerTime":1520926220004},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-96564],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926192666,"answerTime":1520926222672},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-30027],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926191754,"answerTime":1520926221755},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-112942],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926207311,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926224796},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-63059],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926193105,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926221135},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926150134,"answerTime":1520926180136},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-97432],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-82815],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926193091,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926221760},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-106421],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926207315,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926230308},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-103667],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926196219,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926222555},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-100233],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926193272,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1520926223072},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-111759],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926201078,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926223767},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-62959],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:23 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926202313,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926224285},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-69880],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926196010,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926225330},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-106406],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926211029,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926225453},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-14426],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926201652,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926226409},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:26 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:26 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-50369],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:26 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926199169,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926225801},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:26 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:26 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-107275],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:26 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926205380,"answerTime":1520926235386},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-73509],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926205656,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926227798},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-102712],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926199510,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926227885},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-110864],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520919005998,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520919025448},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-33193],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926199992,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926229546},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-122704],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926198497,"answerTime":1520926228502},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-69438],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926217071,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926228488},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-84836],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926210673,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926229271},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-63068],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926217697,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926229647},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-43157],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926202145,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926229515},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-117426],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926223145,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926228870},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-103158],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926258296,"answerTime":1520926288301},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926199904,"answerTime":1520926229905},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-104321],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-113947],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926199912,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926228999},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-83286],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926247137,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926270599},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-73381],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926230883,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926231281},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-103558],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926201543,"answerTime":1520926231547},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-81676],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926210821,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926233119},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-22300],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926203963,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926233685},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-101068],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926402634,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926431032},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-74955],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926203463,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926233052},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-109856],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926207661,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926234164},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-100318],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926204284,"answerTime":1520926234285},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-116149],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926209238,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926235131},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-74486],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926207850,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926235398},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-122157],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926206728,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926235243},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-118513],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926233296,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520926235189},"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-105452],"sessionId":"1","userId":38,"instanceId":"gXP6msSSxsdxhZj8v","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520922413148,"answerTime":1520922443149},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-60882],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926214568,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926236196},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-136493],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926210431,"answerTime":1520926240433},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-97875],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926231005,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926238973},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-7969],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926207534,"answerTime":1520926237549},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-84268],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926210640,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926237233},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-129024],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926216310,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926238406},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926291318,"answerTime":1520926321320},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-33763],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-102848],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926205958,"answerTime":1520926235972},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-114597],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926212142,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926237798},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-128995],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926211605,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926240590},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-117714],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926208680,"answerTime":1520926238684},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-86730],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926208752,"answerTime":1520926238754},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-67612],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520922608381,"answerTime":1520922638396},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-119600],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926224563,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926240231},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-115902],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926213755,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926240061},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-122225],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926210548,"answerTime":1520926240553},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-136421],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926235962,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926245724},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-9763],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926204149,"answerTime":1520926234150},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-101211],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926212697,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926241495},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-128979],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926212356,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926233635},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-141337],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926222034,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926241237},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-115768],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926221081,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926242078},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-63472],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926213544,"answerTime":1520926243549},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-143435],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926218419,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926241846},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-100463],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926218273,"answer":{"choice":"Iris"},"answerTime":1520926241575},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-48923],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926229820,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926240754},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-10937],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926224723,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926245233},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-50539],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926219394,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926243385},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-135260],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926237131,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926245036},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-82391],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926214843,"answerTime":1520926244844},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-79081],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926218525,"answerTime":1520926248531},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-133254],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926243254,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926245445},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-117960],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926214105,"answerTime":1520926244111},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-126395],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926219106,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926245765},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-140240],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926240984,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926249791},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-16777],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926239238,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926247955},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-137741],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926222290,"answer":{"choice":"Walter"},"answerTime":1520926249534},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520922620418,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520922648380},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-57251],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-116634],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926228420,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926248638},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-70588],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926225775,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926248739},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-85923],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926247465,"answer":{"choice":"Iris"},"answerTime":1520926249131},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-119627],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926272600,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926290125},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-90907],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520919027463,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520919047129},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-52859],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926237395,"answer":{"choice":"Kevin"},"answerTime":1520926258285},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-94399],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926223786,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926250680},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:50 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:50 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-139838],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:50 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926220689,"answerTime":1520926250692},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:50 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:50 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-147968],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:50 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926231912,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926250991},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-133027],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926249958,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926250826},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-138609],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926220791,"answerTime":1520926250792},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-140520],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926232314,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926260110},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-131464],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926242605,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926255413},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-130522],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926227335,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926252784},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-131856],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926251149,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520926252839},"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-121318],"sessionId":"1","userId":28,"instanceId":"eiw5o77MEmwmvevEr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926226799,"answerTime":1520926256801},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-93068],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926252830,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520926253573},"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-139352],"sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926253000,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926253546},"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-133574],"sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926182139,"answerTime":1520926212140},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-112817],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926223765,"answerTime":1520926253765},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-136424],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926225079,"answerTime":1520926255081},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-141765],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926226304,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926255508},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-99085],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926231549,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926257136},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-148292],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926252798,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926255830},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:56 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:56 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-143552],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:56 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926230489,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926256570},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:56 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:56 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-110917],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:56 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926227461,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926257235},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-44201],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926229808,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926257468},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[7,-130372],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926240415,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926258380},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-51729],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926248296,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926257074},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-8792],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926231649,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926258526},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-70034],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926251806,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1520926260431},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-25402],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926227833,"answerTime":1520926257837},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-137292],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926236174,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926260463},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-124608],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926233613,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926259320},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-107384],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926237409,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926260464},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-145212],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926235646,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926251931},"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-157622],"sessionId":"1","userId":5,"instanceId":"Ra6gz57dWK6BcRagr","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926229890,"answerTime":1520926259891},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-140868],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926230536,"answerTime":1520926260539},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-99451],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926244082,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926260554},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-79945],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520919049134,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520919058432},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-62157],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926231274,"answerTime":1520926261274},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-93071],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926231518,"answerTime":1520926261535},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-147445],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926247040,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926262015},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-97366],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926231008,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926260610},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-112888],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926290343,"answerTime":1520926320347},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-134339],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926235063,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926262015},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-136810],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926235126,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926262684},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-49858],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926240760,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926262207},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-89059],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926214144,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926221501},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-120174],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926242468,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926266865},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-122273],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926239804,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926263460},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-152651],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926433039,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1520926461534},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-103451],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926257093,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926263783},"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-148456],"sessionId":"1","userId":20,"instanceId":"j33gLLDHBxA8pqbEw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:03 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":3,"instanceId":"MQTL9S67Ge4mDjooZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926242559,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926264719},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-158582],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926235690,"answerTime":1520926265692},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-131072],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926237249,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926264944},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-146208],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926242243,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926265955},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[7,-139615],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926243499,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926265566},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-151046],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926236328,"answerTime":1520926266338},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-146170],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926223502,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926224576},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-121248],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926242764,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926263980},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-32153],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520922445158,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922473524},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-89249],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926243577,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926265794},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-71141],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:07 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926247732,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926272896},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-34927],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:07 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926237989,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1520926266411},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-143019],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926238200,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926267759},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-166052],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926262442,"answer":{"choice":"Kevin"},"answerTime":1520926270650},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-33610],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926239569,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926269555},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-114255],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926257424,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926271865},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-144964],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926323362,"answerTime":1520926353363},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-132856],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926226578,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926228069},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-122740],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926250642,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926270167},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-90114],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926245393,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926270358},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-160226],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926236158,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926263421},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926240699,"answerTime":1520926270711},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-128475],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-116744],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926259139,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926272091},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520922640412,"answerTime":1520922670428},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-149618],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-161244],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:10 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926259485,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926271477},"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[8,-142365],"sessionId":"1","userId":26,"instanceId":"EvuG3terrFz7BhFqn","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520922650384,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922671582},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-137834],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926242067,"answerTime":1520926272069},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-152235],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926230072,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926231154},"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-123822],"sessionId":"1","userId":46,"instanceId":"W9Lg2tDrCdD2frycy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926252690,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926272964},"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-160114],"sessionId":"1","userId":4,"instanceId":"gQf7ZevLMWa83uW4W","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926250745,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926274468},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-109646],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926245567,"answerTime":1520926275573},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-173443],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926243859,"answerTime":1520926273860},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-130464],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:14 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926250547,"answer":{"choice":"Iris"},"answerTime":1520926278558},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-161265],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926257832,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926274470},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-160191],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926264019,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926275596},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-108943],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926247253,"answerTime":1520926277255},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-80560],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926246865,"answerTime":1520926276867},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-109088],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926246153,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926275032},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:17 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:17 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-155275],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:17 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926247776,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926277790},"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-170256],"sessionId":"1","userId":11,"instanceId":"L48Hy5dDAY3kmyLa5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926263547,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926278790},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-162688],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926276475,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926278998},"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:19 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:19 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-162714],"sessionId":"1","userId":19,"instanceId":"6fsmuHWeGrFy49S9r","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:19 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926251537,"answerTime":1520926281539},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-87255],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926292128,"answerTime":1520926322129},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-120909],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926260292,"answerTime":1520926290293},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-124401],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926252699,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926282108},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-177377],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"3voo246ERGT7k66au","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926262124,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926290450},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-159791],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926280802,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926283036},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-164923],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926277594,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926284744},"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:23 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:23 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-180593],"sessionId":"1","userId":2,"instanceId":"TK7zwF5CjssScgFx4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:23 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926259156,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926283420},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-33060],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926264210,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926284465},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-109314],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926254789,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926284572},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-161640],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926268872,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926289034},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-142435],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926258820,"answerTime":1520926288823},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-123078],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926255774,"answerTime":1520926285775},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-166428],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926257534,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926286174},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:26 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:26 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-127726],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:26 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926266950,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926286828},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-166086],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926258585,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926287271},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:27 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:27 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-139603],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:27 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926259875,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926287453},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-164872],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926277601,"answer":{"choice":"Iris"},"answerTime":1520926288951},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-120293],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926259240,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926288599},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-73560],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926261899,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926289038},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-168007],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926274899,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926294696},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-54724],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926260399,"answerTime":1520926290364},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-81696],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926285043,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926289943},"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-169824],"sessionId":"1","userId":15,"instanceId":"TcRmJxdEutLhwyehz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:29 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926260527,"answerTime":1520926290528},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-100036],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926355376,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926374353},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-151835],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926262469,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926291885},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-154024],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926267572,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926291604},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-175079],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926261334,"answerTime":1520926291342},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-137415],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926262470,"answerTime":1520926292480},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-175223],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926265985,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926289977},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-56145],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926262559,"answerTime":1520926292562},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-129461],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926262563,"answerTime":1520926292570},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-109953],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926265466,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926292622},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-179807],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926269761,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926292487},"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-188778],"sessionId":"1","userId":7,"instanceId":"TxTE4hgWjcgMH9sJF","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520919060442,"answerTime":1520919090447},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-92166],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926263282,"answerTime":1520926293283},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-123074],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926264686,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926293904},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-79076],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926262613,"answerTime":1520926292631},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-142909],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926322392,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926352208},"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-164156],"sessionId":"1","userId":35,"instanceId":"AsLGtqzvZD9hC6K8C","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926264029,"answerTime":1520926294035},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-166829],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926272367,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926294244},"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-182104],"sessionId":"1","userId":12,"instanceId":"EcZp8Wu7zKJ33DGRm","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926266723,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926295073},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-186932],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520922672444,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922694790},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-171965],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926267961,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926295963},"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[8,-167618],"sessionId":"1","userId":33,"instanceId":"iox7z68m5zt4GWMLZ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926268415,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926293900},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-168504],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926463546,"answerTime":1520926493548},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-133459],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520922475527,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922502645},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-116367],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926286471,"answer":{"choice":"Iris"},"answerTime":1520926296967},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-119810],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926267703,"answerTime":1520926297704},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-161076],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926267799,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926295820},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-99162],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926265438,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926290356},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-153393],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520922673586,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922697470},"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-161718],"sessionId":"1","userId":25,"instanceId":"K84sJtBAHeuTLS4vv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926274096,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926299191},"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-186340],"sessionId":"1","userId":9,"instanceId":"eZTz8ud6QM7CcXerz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926268362,"answerTime":1520926298365},"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-176181],"sessionId":"1","userId":17,"instanceId":"7sbBW4kbvSHDspjpC","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926272173,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926298445},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-116387],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926272655,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926301098},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-62053],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926285471,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926298898},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-46500],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926293610,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926300105},"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-181575],"sessionId":"1","userId":24,"instanceId":"PPW29FGADszBYLPwG","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926273872,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926302800},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-173893],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"mGarKBe47x6AgCSk2","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926271568,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926301543},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-144231],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:40 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926272723,"answerTime":1520926302731},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-146754],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926279312,"answer":{"choice":"Kevin"},"answerTime":1520926305124},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:43 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:43 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-106377],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:43 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926274100,"answerTime":1520926304102},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-182243],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926293900,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926306431},"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-166555],"sessionId":"1","userId":40,"instanceId":"KRoRhNnazYKufpSc7","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926290953,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520926306123},"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-135463],"sessionId":"1","userId":58,"instanceId":"Gmfi4mEsa9hfXkxCt","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926276473,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926305790},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-138965],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926275871,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926305457},"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-160050],"sessionId":"1","userId":42,"instanceId":"m3qg9H2Jhf3sm9asB","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926298973,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926306628},"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-127465],"sessionId":"1","userId":61,"instanceId":"to2cTvPdNYWQ9ehJA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926280569,"answerTime":1520926310575},"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-191273],"sessionId":"1","userId":10,"instanceId":"5vTqHbfvoeuH9rZfo","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:47 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926278884,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926307083},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:47 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:47 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-137289],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:47 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926277042,"answerTime":1520926307047},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-185296],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926296699,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926314565},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-72590],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926296063,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926309041},"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:49 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:49 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[7,-179808],"sessionId":"1","userId":37,"instanceId":"D9ChqieoG6gAuYojv","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:49 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926324134,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926351197},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:50 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:50 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-147972],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:50 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926291040,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926315869},"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[7,-167265],"sessionId":"1","userId":43,"instanceId":"uNLJXDKjroMqfuTrs","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926283545,"answerTime":1520926312398},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-116110],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926292297,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926321120},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-153224],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926292459,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520926321447},"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-188780],"sessionId":"1","userId":31,"instanceId":"fd9wqseD9sim39Sbk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926292386,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926314487},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-103798],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926287784,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926314623},"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:54 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:54 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-193267],"sessionId":"1","userId":14,"instanceId":"x8DqNd4GBCjy7TXMX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926291982,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926312454},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:54 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:54 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-76618],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926294575,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926315439},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-150329],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926286577,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926315994},"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:56 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:56 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-191058],"sessionId":"1","userId":30,"instanceId":"bxyyyBC3A56h9h4Kg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:56 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926297822,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926315820},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-117161],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926288832,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926317100},"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[7,-194355],"sessionId":"1","userId":21,"instanceId":"A2My9RdiLe8yFXMtu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926290835,"answerTime":1520926320837},"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-153085],"sessionId":"1","userId":53,"instanceId":"duC3NGgnAu42Djcj4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926288186,"answerTime":1520926318189},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-157734],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926289280,"answerTime":1520926319303},"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-169629],"sessionId":"1","userId":44,"instanceId":"X6CvvE4BYrNvgoGy3","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926300948,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926318661},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-64215],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926293405,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926319259},"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-163270],"sessionId":"1","userId":49,"instanceId":"cPiq6ruu4j3NQKQwT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926295906,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926320083},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926294487,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926320253},"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-103253],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-200989],"sessionId":"1","userId":23,"instanceId":"c5DDZooGy7oquvrBW","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:31:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926289468,"answerTime":1520926319471},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-194888],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926290603,"answerTime":1520926320605},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:00 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:00 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-103565],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:00 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926291042,"answerTime":1520926321045},"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-198011],"sessionId":"1","userId":22,"instanceId":"d9y8XMo6borjtCati","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926295290,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926321478},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-149263],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926306129,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926322118},"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-198232],"sessionId":"1","userId":29,"instanceId":"TPb8kgYZRRKv3qGSb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926292531,"answerTime":1520926322532},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-130037],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926376366,"answerTime":1520926406398},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-181871],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926294628,"answer":{"choice":"Petra"},"answerTime":1520926323511},"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-208690],"sessionId":"1","userId":18,"instanceId":"ytMc3vzbNxBkAyL7K","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926307154,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926325738},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-124963],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926294582,"answerTime":1520926324589},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-139961],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520919092470,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520919122009},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-121705],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926294650,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926324654},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-172914],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926300455,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926325964},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-141897],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926318561,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926326033},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-7475],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520922504648,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520922533300},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-145020],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926297075,"answerTime":1520926327076},"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-216935],"sessionId":"1","userId":13,"instanceId":"tnjnaaeRsR3qDCjWK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926295903,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926325444},"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-198046],"sessionId":"1","userId":36,"instanceId":"qoiLhjzG5eHdy6sQS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520922696803,"answerTime":1520922726804},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-201967],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926495569,"answerTime":1520926525571},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-163466],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926303109,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926330978},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-89922],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926299717,"answerTime":1520926329720},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-191082],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926292367,"answerTime":1520926322370},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-183397],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926326595,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926329913},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-143279],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926408407,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926415325},"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:11 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:11 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-188790],"sessionId":"1","userId":39,"instanceId":"3E4voCDZjLYAZ4PLg","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:11 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926327766,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926334520},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-131720],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926303556,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926333358},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-174033],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},0],"startTime":1520926316858,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926337111},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-20254],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926323126,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926341729},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-171827],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926307796,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926333890},"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-165060],"sessionId":"1","userId":57,"instanceId":"rXaK5rGKp7Y93pjCL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926314457,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926331679},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-93841],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:13 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926304740,"answerTime":1520926334746},"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:14 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:14 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-176761],"sessionId":"1","userId":48,"instanceId":"Aq9NzZShdwTKFFjNR","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:14 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926309091,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926335746},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-163945],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926317824,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926334636},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-133973],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926343734,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926344861},"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:16 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:16 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-172954],"sessionId":"1","userId":52,"instanceId":"RygHmAm2JJ2XyqXi4","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:16 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926314409,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926338962},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-140663],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926316571,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926346001},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-102021],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926309091,"answerTime":1520926339096},"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-215315],"sessionId":"1","userId":32,"instanceId":"57Lwf5TTTmBAxSmXA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926336550,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926343603},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:21 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:21 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-138774],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:21 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926353199,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926382516},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-177289],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926316492,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926343127},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:22 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:22 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-130434],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:22 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926320720,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926343686},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-87185],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926317457,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926345535},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-178410],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926320200,"answerTime":1520926350208},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-187748],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926324534,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926350552},"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:30 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:30 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-156055],"sessionId":"1","userId":65,"instanceId":"sXZr3m5hgZdufhrkK","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:30 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926345612,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520926353372},"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-146535],"sessionId":"1","userId":64,"instanceId":"oc34D3jLJNXkKPAvL","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926322087,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926351887},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-133053],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520922535302,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520922558413},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-168131],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:31 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926321511,"answerTime":1520926351514},"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-224899],"sessionId":"1","userId":34,"instanceId":"wpvzeLtzDmh9bXg2R","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926322614,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1520926352540},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-133491],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926327973,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926352692},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-166618],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926323482,"answerTime":1520926353482},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-179265],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926328039,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926354014},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-33450],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},1],"startTime":1520926339119,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926358719},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:34 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:34 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-39854],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:34 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520922728810,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520922754994},"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:35 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:35 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-228151],"sessionId":"1","userId":27,"instanceId":"96twWG8j85CMABFPz","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:35 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926332980,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926358205},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-115148],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520919124012,"answerTime":1520919154015},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:36 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:36 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-151709],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:36 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926326674,"answerTime":1520926356677},"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:37 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:37 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-202920],"sessionId":"1","userId":50,"instanceId":"2aM3LJyA4paHMw5Rw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:37 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926527591,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926556070},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-191946],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926331729,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926359538},"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:39 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:39 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-218893],"sessionId":"1","userId":41,"instanceId":"cgBbBA2Hpj9XkRqmP","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:39 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926324388,"answerTime":1520926354389},"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-213398],"sessionId":"1","userId":45,"instanceId":"ph5SMRzoG2hnvz9DQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926331922,"answerTime":1520926361928},"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:41 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:41 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-173287],"sessionId":"1","userId":6,"instanceId":"ARN64eLFWoF6ADume","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:41 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926336640,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926361668},"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:42 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:42 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-159001],"sessionId":"1","userId":68,"instanceId":"nbkj58F56KcENAPzJ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:42 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926335369,"answerTime":1520926365374},"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:44 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:44 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-204039],"sessionId":"1","userId":47,"instanceId":"Ltd9e42vFfZ9Htoh5","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:44 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926333683,"answerTime":1520926363684},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:45 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:45 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-123846],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:45 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926337757,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926366011},"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-192200],"sessionId":"1","userId":59,"instanceId":"pey2si5a9a4ZuxLTA","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926365695,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926366635},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:48 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:48 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-124786],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:48 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926340969,"answerTime":1520926370970},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:50 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:50 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-170666],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:50 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926368639,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926369476},"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:51 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:51 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-125623],"sessionId":"1","userId":73,"instanceId":"e5QdQr5Fue5MoJnvj","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:51 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926348004,"answerTime":1520926378006},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-132026],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926345131,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926374645},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:53 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:53 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-159948],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:53 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926384517,"answerTime":1520926414518},"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:54 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:54 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-207291],"sessionId":"1","userId":55,"instanceId":"XrzuSitCjMzh9PH8w","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:54 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926345782,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926374824},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-116232],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926347554,"answerTime":1520926377556},"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:57 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:57 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-208428],"sessionId":"1","userId":51,"instanceId":"AEAduM3HPEtpRZGT8","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:57 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926360217,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926381094},"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-136026],"sessionId":"1","userId":74,"instanceId":"D6c8vjtAziWa5v2gN","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:32:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926354700,"answer":{"choice":"Petra"},"answerTime":1520926381357},"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520922560417,"answer":{"choice":"Wendy"},"answerTime":1520922588262},"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-195977],"sessionId":"1","userId":63,"instanceId":"vcvJGTEPzj7nAXHSQ","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-193275],"sessionId":"1","userId":62,"instanceId":"akSKhbN8jk7iF5vTX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926354544,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926381503},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-160451],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926353889,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926382412},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-161576],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926356022,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926382033},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-59461],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926352228,"answerTime":1520926382243},"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-217767],"sessionId":"1","userId":54,"instanceId":"oXWTpAHAGr38Dq99k","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926355489,"answerTime":1520926385489},"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-209267],"sessionId":"1","userId":60,"instanceId":"KNivndMnaoqsXEeho","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520919156028,"answer":{"choice":"Petra"},"answerTime":1520919183572},"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-179254],"sessionId":"1","userId":69,"instanceId":"pNtcCXzGiHaCZgWfy","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},2],"startTime":1520926360722,"answerTime":1520926390726},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[2,-69859],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926558077,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926586358},"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:08 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:08 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-220228],"sessionId":"1","userId":56,"instanceId":"ezXfYYx2BfihBe8TX","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:08 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926376869,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926388170},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-127534],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926372979,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926394268},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:14 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:14 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-191956],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:14 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926380019,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926408515},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:23 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:23 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-160522],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:23 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926384039,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926404149},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:24 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:24 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-79571],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:24 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926376653,"answerTime":1520926406608},"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-189905],"sessionId":"1","userId":70,"instanceId":"R8bMDvwATxg9GKjXb","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926390194,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926405406},"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:26 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:26 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-142748],"sessionId":"1","userId":75,"instanceId":"9Ajk39hpuxF7tj2KT","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:26 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","sessionId":"1","userId":16,"instanceId":"uqtEfQtWMc6KNcQ24","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:28 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926383510,"answer":{"choice":"Laura"},"answerTime":1520926412522},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-189464],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},3],"startTime":1520926392752,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926416430},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:32 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:32 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-93537],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:32 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926384419,"answerTime":1520926414421},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-191580],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926396275,"answerTime":1520926426281},"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:46 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:46 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[0,-221964],"sessionId":"1","userId":66,"instanceId":"po84K9c3Ja7Fy5pHS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:46 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926406151,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926430623},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:50 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:50 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-104043],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:50 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926410517,"answerTime":1520926440519},"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-190527],"sessionId":"1","userId":72,"instanceId":"oirqDNKkDvJsLnjuu","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:33:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926414530,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1520926441715},"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[1,-216650],"sessionId":"1","userId":71,"instanceId":"ECk7B9qDDC3QA4xGS","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},4],"startTime":1520926418434,"answer":{"choice":"Manuel"},"answerTime":1520926446541},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:02 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:02 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-121644],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:02 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926416425,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926444672},"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:04 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:04 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[6,-219827],"sessionId":"1","userId":67,"instanceId":"4Ao7ont9xhdoMjwXk","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:04 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926448542,"answer":{"choice":"Harold"},"answerTime":1520926449892},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:06 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:06 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[3,-122994],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:06 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926451895,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926453072},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-124172],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},5],"startTime":1520926432627,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926452473},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-123889],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},7],"startTime":1520926455075,"answer":{"choice":"Petra"},"answerTime":1520926456290},"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:12 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:12 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[4,-125387],"sessionId":"1","userId":76,"instanceId":"B6dcDHMjsX8M3jB3i","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:12 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>","answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}]},6],"startTime":1520926454475,"answer":{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1520926468676},"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:28 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:28 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjeorr7du001407y0cxztbht6","value":[5,-138091],"sessionId":"1","userId":77,"instanceId":"gqYPAyuv8BQwff2Cw","timestamp":"Tue, 13 Mar 2018 07:34:28 GMT"}
